http://www.bressingham.co.uk/privacy

Kids Club Application
Buy Tickets »
Home
»
Privacy
Privacy
This privacy statement tells you what to expect when we process your personal information. This is the main privacy statement for Athelington Hall, however, some of our services may have additional privacy notices which will be provided to you when you engage or register for such a service. It is important for you to read this statement in full to understand how we use your data and your rights in relation to your data.
Your privacy is important to us
We need to process personal data in order to deliver our services to you:
To allow users to purchase merchandise on this website
To allow users to send us enquiries
To allow users to receive our email newsletter service
We are committed to treating your information securely, with respect and in line with data protection law.
We keep this privacy notice under regular review and we will place all updates of this page on the website as soon as it practicable.
For further information you can contact us as follows:
Organisation address
Bressingham Steam & GardensLow RoadBressinghamDissNorfolkUKIP22 2AB
Telephone: 01379 686900
Email: info@bressingham.co.uk
For independent advice about data protection issues, you can contact the Information Commissioner:
Information CommissionerWycliffe House, Water LaneWilmslowCheshire SK9 5AF
Phone: 0303 123 1113
Email: casework@ico.org.uk
Website: www.ico.org.uk
What information is collected and how it is used?
Bressingham will only collect personal information when we need it. The type of information we need from you will relate purely to contact information allowing us to communicate with you. When we ask you for information, we will make it clear why we need it. We only collect personal information when you complete forms on this website, either when you wish to sign up to our newsletter, purchase anything from us or send us a comment.
Purchasing merchandise from us:
we will need your name, email address and postal address and phone number
it is in our legitimate interests for us to store and use this information as the basis of ongoing communication with you in order to arrange details of a proposed sale.
Sending us a comment:
we will need your name and email address.
we will use this information only if we need to reply to your comment.
Receive email updates / newsletters:
we will need your name and email address.
we need your consent to be added to our emailing lists.
we will use this information to provide you with emails and newsletters relevant to Bressingham and its shops and services
How we will protect the information about you?
We will apply appropriate technical and organisational measures to ensure your personal information is secure.  For example, we have systems in place to ensure that access to personal information is restricted to authorised individuals on a strictly need-to-know basis.
When we need to share personal data with our contractors and third party suppliers, our relationships are governed by our contracts with them which include strict data sharing and confidentiality protocols.
To help us ensure confidentiality of your personal information we may ask you (and any of your representatives) security questions to confirm your identity when you call us and as may be necessary when we call you.
We will not discuss your personal information with anyone other than you, unless you have given us prior written authorisation to do so or where we have received a clear verbal instruction from you (as a one-off circumstance).
Who will we share your information with?
We never share personal information with other organisations for third-party marketing purposes.
Sometimes we will need to share personal information we hold about you with other organisations that we work with or who provide services on our behalf.  When sharing information we will comply with all aspects of current data protection law. All our data sharing relationships are governed by contracts which include strict data sharing and confidentiality protocols.
Where ‘sharing’ is in our ‘legitimate business interests’, we may share your information without seeking your consent first.  This may be with:
Police, HMRC and other relevant authorities.
We may also share information when required by law for example where ordered by the Court or to protect an individual from immediate harm.
What are your rights in relation to your data?
We are committed to upholding your rights in respect of your personal data.
The right to be informed
Through the provision of this and other privacy notices on the website, we will be open and transparent about how and why we use your personal information.
The right of access
You have a right to ask us what personal information we hold about you and to request a copy of your information. This is known as a ‘subject access request’ (SAR).
SARs need to be made in writing and we ask that your written request is accompanied by proof of your address and identity.
If you are seeking to obtain specific information (e.g. about a particular matter or from a particular time period), it helps if you clarify the details of what you would like to receive in your written request.
If someone is requesting information on your behalf they will need written confirmation from you to evidence your consent for us to release this and proof of ID (both yours and theirs).
We have 30 calendar days within which to provide you with the information you’ve asked for (although we will try to provide this to you as promptly as possible).
The right to rectification
You can ask us to rectify your personal data if it is inaccurate or incomplete. Please help us to keep our records accurate by keeping us informed if your details change.
The right to erasure
The right to erasure is also known as ‘the right to be forgotten’. In some circumstances, you can ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is no compelling reason for its continued processing.  This is not an absolute right, and we will need to consider the circumstances of any such request and balance this against our need to continue processing the data.  Our response will also be guided by the provisions of our retention schedule.
The right to object
You can tell us you object to us processing your data to provide auction update emails.
You can specifically opt-out of emails at any time by following the link at the bottom of each email.
How long will you keep my data?
We only hold records during the period of our relationship and for a set period afterwards to allow us to meet our legal obligations, including resolving any follow up issues between us. If you opt out of email updates and newsletters your data is removed from processing immediately.
Please contact us if you would like any more information.
What cookies do we use?
To make this site simpler to use, we sometimes place small files on your computer. These are known as cookies, almost all websites do this too. Cookies have many uses and most are not damaging to your privacy, all of the cookies used on this web site fall into that category. We do not use cookies that collect or transfer your personal data to other web sites for advertising or any other purpose.
Cookies are used on this site purely to improve services for you through, for example:
enabling a service to recognise your device so you don't have to give the same information several times during one task
recognising that you may already have given a username and password so you don't need to do it for every web page requested
measuring how many people are using the site, so it can be made easier to use and there's enough capacity to ensure it is fast enough
We use Google Analytics to measure how many people use this site. We do this to make sure the site is meeting users' needs and to understand how we could improve it.
Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. We do not collect or store any personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are. We also do not allow Google to use or share our analytics data.
The following cookies are used by Google Analytics:
_utma stores a randomly generated number for 2 years
_utmb stores a randomly generated number for 30 minutes
_utmc stores a randomly generated number until you close your browser
_utmz stores a randomly generated number and anonymous information on how the site was reached (e.g. direct or via a link or a search) for 6 months
The following cookie is used to provide other normal website functions:
asp.net_sessionid stores a randomly generated number until you close your browser
If you do not wish to accept any cookies on to your machine you can disable them by adjusting the settings on your browser. However this is likely to adversely affect the functionality of websites you visit.
For further information visit: www.allaboutcookies.org
Visit Our Beautiful Gardens
Gifts from our shop
Sign up for email updates
Enter our free monthly prize draw for a family ticket!
See what's happening right now!
View our galleries
